A Finding Aid to the C. J. (Clarence Joseph) Bulliet Papers, circa 1888-1959, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bullclar
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, 1909-1952; Series 6; 7.7 Linear feet Boxes 27-34, 36-37
  - Printed Material by Others, 6.2
    - Books (Box 28)
      - Esto Publishing Company, Enjoy Your Museum Pamphlets (IV-VIIB), 1934-1935 (Box 28, Folder 23)
      - Faure, Elie, A. Derain, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Gill, Eric and Denis Teg., Unholy Trinity (1938); Henry E. Huntington Library & Art Gallery, Handbook of the Art Collections (1941), 1938, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Indiana Artists Club, Biographical Directory of Indiana Artists (1937); Jacques, Bertha E., Concerning Etchings (1927); Kahn, Otto, About Art (1927), 1927-1937 (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - M. Knoedler & Company, Inc., Six Modern Masters, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Seigmeister, Ellie, Music and Society (1938); United Nations, Declaration universalle des droits de l'homme (1949), 1938, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Walsh, George D. and David C. Bennett, A Tour Among the Thousand Islands, circa 1888-1959 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Clippings (Box 28)
      - About or Mentioning C. J. Bulliet, 1918-1962 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Miscellaneous Topics (art-related), 1913-1952 (Box 28, Folder 31-35)
      - Miscellaneous Topics (not art-related), 1913-1952 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Reviews of Books by Bulliet, 1918-1952 (Box 28, Folder 37-38)
    - Exhibitions, Chicago (Box 28)
      - Announcements and Invitations, 1928-1959 (Box 28, Folder 39-42)
      - Catalogs, 1915-1951 (Box 29, Folder 1-17)
      - Catalogs, circa 1888-1959 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
      - Prospectuses, 1931-1950 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Other Exhibitions (Box 30)
      - Announcements and Invitations, 1929-1951 (Box 30, Folder 5-8)
      - Catalogs, 1911-1930 (Box 30, Folder 9-20)
      - Catalogs, 1931-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1-17)
      - Catalogs, circa 1888-1959 (Box 32, Folder 1-9)
      - Prospectuses, 1934-1942 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Items (Box 32)
      - Advertisements and Announcements of Books by Bulliet, 1927-1938 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Announcements, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Catalogs of Reproductions for Sale, circa 1888-1959 (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Invitations, 1934-1947 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Programs for Talks by Bulliet, 1933 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Museum Publications (Box 32)
      - Allen Memorial Art Museum, Oberlin College, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana, John Herron Art Institute, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Art Institute of Chicago, 1930-1952 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1930-1931 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Buffalo Fine Arts Academy, Albright Art Gallery, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - City Art Museum of St. Louis, 1934-1949 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1934-1950 (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Field Museum of Natural History, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 23)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1930-1938 (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Milwaukee Art Institute, 1927-1937 (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1934 (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Museum of Art, Portland, Oregon, 1935-1941 (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1930-1935 (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - National Academy of Design, 1936 (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Newark Museum of Science, Art, Industry, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - San Francisco Art Association, San Francisco Museum of Art, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1941-1942 (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Periodicals (Box 32)
      - All Arts Magazine, (1925); All the News (Daily News Guild Unit, 1950-1951), 1925-1951 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - American Artist (American Artists' Congress), 1937 (Box 32, Folder 35)
        Oversized material in Box 37
      - American Art Student and Commercial Artist, 1924-1925 (Box 32, Folder 36-37)
      - American Chamber of Commerce Journal (1934); The Argus (1927-1928); Art and Industry (1924-1944) (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Art and Life (1924); Art and Understanding (1930); Art Bulletin (Equity of Chicago Artists) (1935), 1924-1935 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Art Center Bulletin, 1926-1927 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Art Digest, 1927-1952 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Art Gallery Magazine (Grand Central Art Galleries), 1925 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Artistry (1936); Artists Equity News (1934); Artlover (J. B. Neuman, Inc., undated); Art Lovers' Magazine (1925), 1925-1936 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Art News, 1925-1928 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Art News and Review (1950-1952); Art Notes (Macbeth Gallery) (1924-1930), 1924-1952 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Arts (1924-1925); Art Students League News (1950-1952); Axis (1935), 1924-1952 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - B'nai Brith Magazine, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Bulletin (Chicago Guild of Freelance Artists, 1937); Bulletin of the Bachstitz Gallery (1924), 1924-1937 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Bulletin of the Rhode Island School of Design (1926, 1930); Bulletin of the Smith College Museum of Art (1932, 1934), 1926-1934 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Bulletin of the Society of Arts and Crafts (1927); The Burr McIntosh Monthly (1909); The Carmel Cymbal (1926); The Checkerboard (Weyhe Gallery, undated), 1909-1927 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Chicago Artist (1937-1938); The Chicago Chronicle (1926), 1926-1938 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Chicago Women's Aid Weekly Bulletin (1942); Colour Magazine (1924); Crecendo (1944); Doubt (1931); Four Arts (1934); Gallery Notes (John Mitchell, 1946), 1924-1946 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Handicraft (1912); Integrity (1949); Intermission, (1933); International Studio, (1925), 1912-1949 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Kapustkan (1941); La Revue Moderne (1938); L'Art Vivant (1925), 1925-1941 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Le Figaro Artistique, 1925-1926 (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
      - Le Gaulois Artistique (1929); Les artists d'aujour d'hui (1928); Magazine of Art, (1947-1948); The Measure, A Journal of Poetry (1921); Milch Gallery Art News, (1924-1929), 1921-1948 (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - New American (1935); The News Bulletin (Artists Guild of Chicago) (1952), 1935-1952 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - New York Art Herald Art Supplement (European Edition), 1925 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Palette and Chisel, 1925-1932 (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Patron's Supplement (Associated American Artists, undated); Pictures on Exhibit (1939-1942) (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Print-Collector's Bulletin, 1930-1934 (Box 33, Folder 23)
      - Publisher's Weekly (1927); The Phi Beta Kappa Key (1928); Real America (1933); Renaissance Society of the University of Chicago Bulletin (1930); Revue du Vrai et du Beau Arts et Lettres (1924), 1924-1933 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Right Angle (1949); Schaeffer Galleries Bulletin (1947); Section of Fine Arts Bulletin (1941); The Studio (1942); The TPROA Quill (1928); Technicolor News and Views (1952), 1928-1952 (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Trends and Tides (1950); True Tales of the Arts (1925); The Villager (1924); The Visitor (St. Luke's Parish, Evanston, Ill., 1930); Weekly Wrestling News (undated) Western Arts Association Bulletin (1935), 1924-1950 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Press Releases, 1931-1952 (Box 34, Folder 1-11)
    - Oversized Periodicals (Box 37)
      - Oversized American Artist (American Artists' Congress), 1937 (Box 37)
        Oversized material from Box 32, F35
      - Oversized Art News, 1925-1928 (Box 37)
        Oversized material from Box 33, F5
      - Oversized New York Art Herald Art Supplement (European Edition), 1925 (Box 37)
        Oversized material from Box 33, F20
- Artwork, 1916-1948; Series 7; 0.6 Linear feet Boxes 35, 38, OV 39
  Art work, mainly by Chicago area artists, consists of prints, drawings, and a sketchbook, probably given to him by the artists themselves.
  A small number of additional prints and drawings are scattered among the Artist Files (Series 4), and some Christmas cards containing original arts work are with correspondence (Series 2).
  This series has been divided as 3 subseries:
  7.1: Drawings, 1916-1932
  7.2: Prints, 1925-1948
  7.3: Oversized Artwork, 1925-1947
  - Drawings, 1916-1932; 7.1
    - Drawings, A, 1916-1929 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Drawings, B-Z, 1916-1929 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Drawings, 1925-1932 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      Baer, George
      Bahnc, Salcia
      Bonunt, W. Wolfgang
      Ganso, Emil
      Levy, Bea
      Robins, Sophie
      Snyder, Corydon G.
      Unsigned
    - Oversized Drawing by Todros Geller, circa 1888-1959 (Box OV 39)
  - Prints, 1925-1948; 7.2
    - Prints, A-G, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Prints, H-I, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Prints, K-N, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Prints, O, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Prints, P-Z, 1925-1948 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Artwork, 1925-1947; 7.3
    - Oversized Artwork, 1925-1947 (Box 38, Folder 3-7)
      Berger, D.
      Cassody, Edithe Jane
      Evans, Dulah Llan
      Foy, Frances Geller, Todros
      Glaman, Eugenie
      Heller, Helen West
      Hoeckner, Carl
      Jacobs, William
      Jacques, Bertha E.
      Maje
      Overall, Charles
      Page, Grover
      Pescheret, Leon R.
      Plascshke, Paul A.
      Prusheck, Harvey George
      Thoglum, Jean
      Wiralt, Edward
    - Oversized Artwork, circa 1888-1959 (Box OV 39)
      Dehn, Adolph
      Rose, Iver